<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts | Industrial AI Group @UOA</title>
    <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Posts</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://uoa-iai.github.io/media/icon_hubb891712c49b4784dd7e680d44157331_31819_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab visit from Christopher Luxon, Leader of the National Party</title>
      <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/luxon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/luxon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On October 17, 2022, Christopher Luxon, Leader of the New Zealand National Party and Leader of the opposition, visited our team. We showcased our research outcomes and impact we created for New Zealand.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We are hosting 2023 IEEE CASE Conference in Auckland</title>
      <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/ieee-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/ieee-case/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;_automation-for-a-resilient-society_&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Automation for a Resilient Society&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are excited that the 19th International Conference on Automation Science and Engineering (CASE) will be hosted in Auckland, New Zealand on &lt;strong&gt;26th August - 29th August, 2023&lt;/strong&gt;. The upcoming conference theme is &amp;ldquo;Automation for a Resilient Society&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IEEE CASE 2023 will be held in Auckland, giving attendees a chance to learn about Aotearoa New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s cutting-edge innovations and automation in the fields of manufacturing, agriculture, aquaculture, forestry, infrastructure, and healthcare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the Organising Committee Chair, Dr. Yuqian Lu is committed to making IEEE CASE 2023 and unforgettable experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;For more information, visit the&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://case2023.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CASE 2023 Website&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MBIE Endeavor Fund Success: $10.3 million investment to transform construction</title>
      <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/mbie-fund/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/mbie-fund/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HERA-led research programme, &amp;ldquo;Developing a Construction 4.0 transformation of Aotearoa New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s construction sector&amp;rdquo;, has been successful in the 2022 round of the prestigious Endeavour Fund. The $10.3 million grant will support the four-year Construction 4.0 research project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The project, which the Industrial AI Research Team is part of, is centred on improving the productivity of Aotearoa New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s construction industry using Construction 4.0 approaches. The project outcomes will benefit the construction sector with better economic performance, building and infrastructure affordability and enhanced communication of stakeholders for enhancements in productivity and output quality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Industrial AI Research Team will be a key part in delivering construction automation digitalisation solutions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Read more on the&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.hera.org.nz/research-endeavour-fund/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;article&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A mobile manipulator to help workers on the factory floor</title>
      <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/mobile-manipulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/mobile-manipulator/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What if you had a robot assistant that could help you use a screwdriver, pick things off a shelf, and carry things around a factory? It might not be something out of a science-fiction novel too much longer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr Yuqian Lu from the Department of Mechanical Engineering is creating a mobile robot that can do just that. The robot has built-in intelligence to navigate around people and obstacles, think and act autonomously. Lu wants to create a robot that can work alongside humans as part of a human-robot team to meet New Zealand’s industry needs better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Traditional automation techniques are efficient for creating standardised products at large volume: cars, phones, and more. But that doesn’t work for lots of New Zealand manufacturers. Many New Zealand manufacturers are smaller than their overseas counterparts and make highly customised products with manual or semi-automated manufacturing processes. “You may be surprised to see the amount of manual and repetitive work in the factories of some of the most innovative high-tech companies”, Dr Lu says.&lt;/p&gt;

   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   &lt;figure  &gt;
     &lt;div class=&#34;d-flex justify-content-center&#34;&gt;
       &lt;div class=&#34;w-100&#34; &gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; srcset=&#34;
                  /post/mobile-manipulator/mobile_manipulator_hu8571d454dca6e406c99cc541fc63b1db_118177_8673882b91ed9e666f2e3491151b4d43.webp 400w,
                  /post/mobile-manipulator/mobile_manipulator_hu8571d454dca6e406c99cc541fc63b1db_118177_632b1671ed6a73f86f15fa3e6e2e65fe.webp 760w,
                  /post/mobile-manipulator/mobile_manipulator_hu8571d454dca6e406c99cc541fc63b1db_118177_1200x1200_fit_q80_h2_lanczos.webp 1200w&#34;
                  src=&#34;https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/mobile-manipulator/mobile_manipulator_hu8571d454dca6e406c99cc541fc63b1db_118177_8673882b91ed9e666f2e3491151b4d43.webp&#34;
                  width=&#34;760&#34;
                  height=&#34;428&#34;
                  loading=&#34;lazy&#34; data-zoomable /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s generally not technically or commercially viable for these manufacturers to invest in expensive standardised automation technologies. So, Dr Lu, with his colleagues from the Laboratory of Industry 4.0 Smart Manufacturing Lab at the Faculty of Engineering, proposed a solution. What if they built a flexible and intelligent robot that could help with many different jobs and move from project to project?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this reason, an autonomous mobile robot allows manufacturers an unprecedented level of flexibility. It can be integrated with already-existing manufacturing cells to co-manipulate manual work. New Zealand small manufacturers can introduce flexible robots gradually, test them out, and take their own steps towards automating their facilities. Dr Lu is also working on teaching his robots to autonomously learn new tasks in a factory to better support human operators.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr Lu’s goal is that the mobile robot will soon work as an assistant or as part of a team with human workers. He envisions it helping screw things in and working safely around human operators to free them of tedious and repetitive work, among other tasks. “We want to create a human-robot collaboration,” Dr Lu said.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RCIM Best Paper Award</title>
      <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/rcimaward/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/rcimaward/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Best Paper is awarded each year to the RCIM paper published in the past seven-year with the highest number of citations measured in Scopus over the past five years. This is a significant achievement for our work on Smart Manufacturing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.rcim.2019.101837&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Published version&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; / &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/334759247_Digital_twin-driven_smart_manufacturing_Connotation_reference_model_applications_and_research_issues&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preprint version&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Science for Technological Innovation National Science Challenge (SfTI) Grant</title>
      <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/sfti/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/sfti/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Industrial AI Team @ UOA was awarded the prestigious SfTI seed grant over two years to advance time-sensitive industrial control technologies in 5G environment, in collaboration with Victoria University of Wellington, Spark New Zealand and Nokia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Project Title: Ultra-reliable time-sensitive industrial control in the cloud&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Public Statement: As the momentum of 5G builds, a range of applications will be developed. These include real-time cloud-controlled industrial systems and self-driving vehicles. The need is for 5G technology to provide robust and time-sensitive data transmission over wide area networks (WANs). This is to ensure the systems and vehicles can interact simultaneously without, for example, arriving out of order or colliding. This project, led by University of Auckland researchers, aims to design a data communication scheduling algorithm and supporting streaming technologies. This will enable time-sensitive transmission of control data for multiple devices over WANs.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
