<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Industry 4.0 | Industrial AI Group @UOA</title>
    <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/tag/industry-4.0/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://uoa-iai.github.io/tag/industry-4.0/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Industry 4.0</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://uoa-iai.github.io/media/icon_hubb891712c49b4784dd7e680d44157331_31819_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Industry 4.0</title>
      <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/tag/industry-4.0/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit from Professor Qiang Huang</title>
      <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/prof-q-huang/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/prof-q-huang/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On December 2, 2022, Professor Qiang Huang, Epstein Department of Industrial and Systems Engineering, University of Southern California (USC), visited our team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Professor Qiang Huang presented a seminar on his work in &amp;ldquo;Engineering-Informed Machine Learning for Additive Manufacturing Accuracy Control.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bio: Professor Qiang Huang was the holder of Gordon S. Marshall Early Career Chair in Engineering at USC from 2012 to 2016. He is also a Department Editor for IISE Transactions and an Associate Editor for ASME Transactions, Journal of Manufacturing Science and Engineering. He has also received various awards including the IISE Fellow and ASME Awards, NSF CAREER award, and 2021 IEEE CASE Best Conference Paper Award, 2013 IEEE Transactions on Automation Science and Engineering Best Paper Award. He has five patents on Machine Learning for Additive Manufacturing (ML4AM).&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab visit from Christopher Luxon, Leader of the National Party</title>
      <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/luxon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/luxon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On October 17, 2022, Christopher Luxon, Leader of the New Zealand National Party and Leader of the opposition, visited our team. We showcased our research outcomes and impact we created for New Zealand.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MBIE Endeavor Fund Success: $10.3 million investment to transform construction</title>
      <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/mbie-fund/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/mbie-fund/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HERA-led research programme, &amp;ldquo;Developing a Construction 4.0 transformation of Aotearoa New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s construction sector&amp;rdquo;, has been successful in the 2022 round of the prestigious Endeavour Fund. The $10.3 million grant will support the four-year Construction 4.0 research project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The project, which the Industrial AI Research Team is part of, is centred on improving the productivity of Aotearoa New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s construction industry using Construction 4.0 approaches. The project outcomes will benefit the construction sector with better economic performance, building and infrastructure affordability and enhanced communication of stakeholders for enhancements in productivity and output quality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Industrial AI Research Team will be a key part in delivering construction automation digitalisation solutions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Read more on the&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.hera.org.nz/research-endeavour-fund/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;article&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
