<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>artificial intelligence | Industrial AI Group @ UOA</title>
    <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/tag/artificial-intelligence/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://uoa-iai.github.io/tag/artificial-intelligence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>artificial intelligence</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://uoa-iai.github.io/media/icon_hubb891712c49b4784dd7e680d44157331_31819_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>artificial intelligence</title>
      <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/tag/artificial-intelligence/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title> Dr. Yuqian Lu Delivers Keynote on Industrial AI at Major Chinese Manufacturing Conference</title>
      <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/keynote-ms2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/keynote-ms2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. Yuqian Lu recently made a significant contribution to a prestigious Chinese academic conference on intelligent manufacturing. The event, titled &amp;ldquo;2024 China Mechanical Engineering Society Industrial Big Data and Intelligent Systems Branch Academic Annual Conference and the 7th Academic Conference on Big Data-Driven Intelligent Manufacturing,&amp;rdquo; was held on July 6, 2024, in Dalian, China.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Lu was one of eight distinguished experts invited to deliver a keynote speech at the conference. His presentation, &amp;ldquo;Illuminating the Machine Mind: A Quantum Leap in Intelligent Manufacturing,&amp;rdquo; was well-received by the audience of scholars and industry elites from across China.&lt;/p&gt;

   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   
   &lt;figure  &gt;
     &lt;div class=&#34;d-flex justify-content-center&#34;&gt;
       &lt;div class=&#34;w-100&#34; &gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; srcset=&#34;
                  /post/keynote-ms2024/1_hu5438825b9b6d1014226d20d231e650c2_237698_eb03158612cc092b010bae93456188c1.webp 400w,
                  /post/keynote-ms2024/1_hu5438825b9b6d1014226d20d231e650c2_237698_45b815013bda6ae4f58513026f8c18cb.webp 760w,
                  /post/keynote-ms2024/1_hu5438825b9b6d1014226d20d231e650c2_237698_1200x1200_fit_q80_h2_lanczos.webp 1200w&#34;
                  src=&#34;https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/keynote-ms2024/1_hu5438825b9b6d1014226d20d231e650c2_237698_eb03158612cc092b010bae93456188c1.webp&#34;
                  width=&#34;760&#34;
                  height=&#34;507&#34;
                  loading=&#34;lazy&#34; data-zoomable /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The conference, which focused on &amp;ldquo;high-performance intelligent manufacturing driven by industrial big data,&amp;rdquo; brought together leading minds in the field to discuss the latest research findings and application prospects of industrial big data and intelligent systems in smart manufacturing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Lu&amp;rsquo;s participation underscores the University of Auckland&amp;rsquo;s position at the forefront of international research in intelligent manufacturing. His insights into the &amp;lsquo;machine mind&amp;rsquo; and its implications for manufacturing processes highlight the potential for quantum advancements in the field.
The conference featured a variety of sessions, including keynote speeches, invited talks, and forum discussions. It provided a platform for academics and industry professionals to exchange ideas and explore collaborative opportunities in areas such as industrial big data, intelligent systems, and advanced manufacturing technologies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Lu&amp;rsquo;s contribution to this high-level academic event not only enhances his personal standing in the field but also strengthens the University of Auckland&amp;rsquo;s reputation as a hub for cutting-edge research in intelligent manufacturing and data-driven technologies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As global interest in smart manufacturing continues to grow, Dr. Lu&amp;rsquo;s participation in this conference demonstrates New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s active role in shaping the future of this critical industry sector.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;talk-abstract&#34;&gt;Talk Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next-generation Artificial Intelligence (AI) technologies are revolutionising human-machine collaboration. This quantum shift in AI capabilities has opened a portal to a world where super-intelligent machines seamlessly integrate with human expertise in the most complex manufacturing environments. Yet, the journey to true machine intelligence in manufacturing is not a mere extension of the AI revolution led by computer scientists. It demands a nuanced, multidisciplinary approach that harmonises technological innovation with industrial intricacies. This talk will explore the driving forces, enabling technologies, and transformative impact of next-generation machine intelligence in manufacturing. We will dive deep into the pioneering work of the Industrial AI Research Group@UoA, unveiling our latest advancements in knowledge understanding, open-source dataset development, machine intelligence algorithm design, and real-world applications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
