<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>grant | Industrial AI Group @ UOA</title>
    <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/category/grant/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://uoa-iai.github.io/category/grant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>grant</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://uoa-iai.github.io/media/icon_hubb891712c49b4784dd7e680d44157331_31819_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>grant</title>
      <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/category/grant/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>We are hiring - full PhD scholarships and post-doc position on human-robot collaboration (MBIE Endeavour Fund)</title>
      <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/mbie_position/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/mbie_position/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are excited that the IAI Research Group has been awarded $1 million over 3 years from Ministry of Business, Innovation and Employment (MBIE) Endeavour Fund to work on “Ultra-flexible human-robot collaborative product assembly”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The manufacturing industry in Aotearoa New Zealand faces a longstanding productivity challenge due to the unsuitability of traditional automation methods for its high-mix-low-volume nature. To address this, we will develop ultra-flexible smooth human-robot collaboration technologies. These innovations will enable seamless interaction between humans and robots in dynamic manufacturing setups, particularly in product assembly, through advanced cognitive capabilities. Robots equipped with real-time human state sensing, reasoning, and adaptive behaviour planning will understand and respond to human physical and cognitive states, enhancing productivity. Multimodal human-robot communication interfaces will ensure accessibility and cultural relevance, including support for te reo Māori.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The team comprises experts in human sensing, robot control, human-machine interactions, and Māori knowledge, ensuring a comprehensive approach. We will collaborate closely with stakeholders throughout the project, including government agencies, industry associations, end-users, consultants, and Māori and Pacific communities. By co-designing the technology with key industry partners, we will ensure its effectiveness and commercial viability. Ultimately, the project seeks to revolutionise manufacturing automation in New Zealand and globally, leading to improved productivity, product quality, and economic benefits. The advanced robot control technologies will also have global applications and can be exported as high-value software packages. Importantly, the project incorporates Tikanga following Māori data sovereignty principles and aims to support workplace well-being for Māori and all New Zealanders, emphasising cultural sensitivity and inclusivity in technology development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Two PhD Scholarships and One Postdoc Research Fellow Position Available&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking for two full scholarship PhD students and one post-doc researcher to join us. Please check the job descriptions for information on project details, candidate requirements and application processes: &lt;a href=&#34;https://uoa-iai.github.io/uploads/2024mbiejobs.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Job Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Application Deadline: &lt;strong&gt;1st November 2024&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For further information, feel free to contact: Dr. Yuqian Lu (&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:yuqian.lu@auckland.ac.nz&#34;&gt;yuqian.lu@auckland.ac.nz&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MBIE Endeavor Fund Success: $10.3 million investment to transform construction</title>
      <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/mbie-fund/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/mbie-fund/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HERA-led research programme, &amp;ldquo;Developing a Construction 4.0 transformation of Aotearoa New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s construction sector&amp;rdquo;, has been successful in the 2022 round of the prestigious Endeavour Fund. The $10.3 million grant will support the four-year Construction 4.0 research project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The project, which the Industrial AI Research Team is part of, is centred on improving the productivity of Aotearoa New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s construction industry using Construction 4.0 approaches. The project outcomes will benefit the construction sector with better economic performance, building and infrastructure affordability and enhanced communication of stakeholders for enhancements in productivity and output quality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Industrial AI Research Team will be a key part in delivering construction automation digitalisation solutions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Read more on the&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.hera.org.nz/research-endeavour-fund/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;article&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Science for Technological Innovation National Science Challenge (SfTI) Grant</title>
      <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/sfti/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/sfti/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Industrial AI Team @ UOA was awarded the prestigious SfTI seed grant over two years to advance time-sensitive industrial control technologies in 5G environment, in collaboration with Victoria University of Wellington, Spark New Zealand and Nokia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Project Title: Ultra-reliable time-sensitive industrial control in the cloud&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Public Statement: As the momentum of 5G builds, a range of applications will be developed. These include real-time cloud-controlled industrial systems and self-driving vehicles. The need is for 5G technology to provide robust and time-sensitive data transmission over wide area networks (WANs). This is to ensure the systems and vehicles can interact simultaneously without, for example, arriving out of order or colliding. This project, led by University of Auckland researchers, aims to design a data communication scheduling algorithm and supporting streaming technologies. This will enable time-sensitive transmission of control data for multiple devices over WANs.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
