<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publication | Industrial AI Group @ UOA</title>
    <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/category/publication/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://uoa-iai.github.io/category/publication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Publication</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://uoa-iai.github.io/media/icon_hubb891712c49b4784dd7e680d44157331_31819_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Publication</title>
      <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/category/publication/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>IJPR Top Trending Article on Industrial Knowledge Graph.</title>
      <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/ipjr-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/ipjr-2023/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Huge congratulations to Dr. Bin Zhou and Prof. Jinsong Bao to this excellent joint work on developing innovative machine learning algorithms to extract knowledge from industrial time series data. This paper has been recognized as a Top Trending Article for 2023 at International Journal of Production Research. We are proud of this achievement from our student group (Dr. Bin Zhou was a PhD student at the time of publication) and long-term collaboration with Prof. Bao.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Groundbreaking Research in Manufacturing Quality Control from Karen Wang</title>
      <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/rootcase-jms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/rootcase-jms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In a significant advancement for the manufacturing industry, Karen Wang, a master&amp;rsquo;s student at the University of Auckland, has developed an innovative approach to root cause analysis of product defects. This breakthrough came as part of her one-year master&amp;rsquo;s study, conducted in collaboration with AspectPL Ltd.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wang&amp;rsquo;s research introduces the product-wise Ensemble Bayesian Network (EBN), a robust and intelligent method for identifying the root causes of manufacturing defects. This novel approach combines Bayesian Networks with ensemble learning techniques, offering a more reliable and interpretable solution to a long-standing challenge in quality control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study, co-authored with Chao Liu from Aston University and Yuqian Lu from the University of Auckland, demonstrates significant improvements in acquiring causal knowledge, identifying root causes with probabilities, and predicting quality risks in production. Tested with real-world data from the plastics industry, the EBN method shows promise for enhancing manufacturing quality and productivity across various sectors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This collaboration between academia and industry showcases the potential for student-led research to drive meaningful innovations in the manufacturing landscape. AspectPL Ltd&amp;rsquo;s involvement underscores the immediate practical applications of Wang&amp;rsquo;s work, bridging the gap between theoretical research and industry needs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As manufacturers worldwide seek to optimize their processes and reduce defects, Wang&amp;rsquo;s contribution represents a timely and valuable tool in the pursuit of excellence in product quality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information on the work, please visit our &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jmsy.2024.06.001&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;open access full paper&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HA-ViD paper accepted at NeurIPS 2023</title>
      <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/havid-neurips/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/havid-neurips/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are pleased to announce the acceptance of our paper, &amp;ldquo;HA-ViD: A Human Assembly Video Dataset for Comprehensive Assembly Knowledge Understanding&amp;rdquo; at the esteemed NeurIPS conference. This achievement marks a milestone in our journey toward understanding the comprehensive knowledge of assembly applications such as human-robot collaboration, robot skill learning and assembly process monitoring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HA-ViD captures the essence of industrial human assembly scenarios through the designed Generic Assembly Box, 3-stage progressive assembly setup and consistent human-robot shared annotations. The applications of this work enables research towards understanding natural human behaviours, progressive knowledge acquisition and two-hand collaboration patterns during assembly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information on HA-ViD, please visit our project &lt;a href=&#34;https://iai-hrc.github.io/ha-vid&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;website&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RCIM Best Paper Award</title>
      <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/rcimaward/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/rcimaward/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Best Paper is awarded each year to the RCIM paper published in the past seven-year with the highest number of citations measured in Scopus over the past five years. This is a significant achievement for our work on Smart Manufacturing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.rcim.2019.101837&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Published version&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; / &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/334759247_Digital_twin-driven_smart_manufacturing_Connotation_reference_model_applications_and_research_issues&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preprint version&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
