<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>root cause analysis | Industrial AI Group @ UOA</title>
    <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/tag/root-cause-analysis/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://uoa-iai.github.io/tag/root-cause-analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>root cause analysis</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://uoa-iai.github.io/media/icon_hubb891712c49b4784dd7e680d44157331_31819_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>root cause analysis</title>
      <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/tag/root-cause-analysis/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Groundbreaking Research in Manufacturing Quality Control from Karen Wang</title>
      <link>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/rootcase-jms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uoa-iai.github.io/post/rootcase-jms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In a significant advancement for the manufacturing industry, Karen Wang, a master&amp;rsquo;s student at the University of Auckland, has developed an innovative approach to root cause analysis of product defects. This breakthrough came as part of her one-year master&amp;rsquo;s study, conducted in collaboration with AspectPL Ltd.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wang&amp;rsquo;s research introduces the product-wise Ensemble Bayesian Network (EBN), a robust and intelligent method for identifying the root causes of manufacturing defects. This novel approach combines Bayesian Networks with ensemble learning techniques, offering a more reliable and interpretable solution to a long-standing challenge in quality control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study, co-authored with Chao Liu from Aston University and Yuqian Lu from the University of Auckland, demonstrates significant improvements in acquiring causal knowledge, identifying root causes with probabilities, and predicting quality risks in production. Tested with real-world data from the plastics industry, the EBN method shows promise for enhancing manufacturing quality and productivity across various sectors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This collaboration between academia and industry showcases the potential for student-led research to drive meaningful innovations in the manufacturing landscape. AspectPL Ltd&amp;rsquo;s involvement underscores the immediate practical applications of Wang&amp;rsquo;s work, bridging the gap between theoretical research and industry needs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As manufacturers worldwide seek to optimize their processes and reduce defects, Wang&amp;rsquo;s contribution represents a timely and valuable tool in the pursuit of excellence in product quality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information on the work, please visit our &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jmsy.2024.06.001&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;open access full paper&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
